Where are you from?
Speak Common.
It's the only way to learn it.
When did they take you?
I want to kill the Masters.
You heard her!
She said she came to free us!
You're a fool.
The Masters are too strong.
She will protect us.
She defeated the Masters' Champion.
She has a great army.
You want to live the rest of your days in chains?
I want to live.
You saw what they did to those children.
What do you think they’ll do to us?
I’ve been through two slave revolts, boy.
They always end the same way:
the Masters in power and the slaves dead.
All men must die.
But I promise you,
a single day of freedom is worth
more than a lifetime in chains.
Who are you?
This one is called Grey Worm.
I was taken as a baby by the Masters of Astapor,
raised and trained as Unsullied.
Now I fight for Daenerys,
the Mother of Dragons
and Breaker of Chains.
You are Unsullied?
They taught you how to fight before you could walk.
We are not soldiers!
We have no training,
no weapons.
There are three slaves in this city for every Master.
No one can give you your freedom, brothers.
If you want it,
you must take it.